<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Azure Readiness starts here...</title>
    <link>https://www.007ffflearning.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Azure Readiness starts here...</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.007ffflearning.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>My Published Azure Books</title>
      <link>https://www.007ffflearning.com/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.007ffflearning.com/books/</guid>
      <description>                     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Published Azure Books</title>
      <link>https://www.007ffflearning.com/publications/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.007ffflearning.com/publications/books/</guid>
      <description>                    Pro Azure Governance Azure Strategy &amp;amp; Implementation Guide Hands On Kubernetes on Azure   * * *        Buy Your Copy Here Get Your FREE copy Here Get Your FREE copy Here   * * *                  Efficiently Migrating to Azure Implementing Azure OMS Azure Infrastructure as Code   * * *        Buy Your Copy Here Buy Your Copy Here [Release date July 2020]         </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Published Azure Videos</title>
      <link>https://www.007ffflearning.com/publications/videos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.007ffflearning.com/publications/videos/</guid>
      <description>                    Architecting an Azure Compute Infrastructure Learning Microsoft Azure Azure Security (Packt)   * * *        Buy Your Copy Here Get Your FREE copy Here [Release date May 2020]             Several Azure Online Courses     * * *        Check Out The List      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Published Azure Videos</title>
      <link>https://www.007ffflearning.com/videos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.007ffflearning.com/videos/</guid>
      <description>Click on the video images for more details                      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>is HTML parameter gone from Logic Apps Send Email Connector</title>
      <link>https://www.007ffflearning.com/post/email-is-html-gone-logicapps/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.007ffflearning.com/post/email-is-html-gone-logicapps/</guid>
      <description>Hi,
For almost 2 years, I have been using the &amp;ldquo;Office 365 Outlook Connector&amp;rdquo; as part of my Logic Apps flows, to send emails internally and externally. Mainly for external receivers, I used the &amp;ldquo;is HTML&amp;rdquo; parameter for the body of the email.
This weekend, I was building a new Logic Apps flow, and to my surprise, finding out that the &amp;ldquo;V2&amp;rdquo; of this same connector / action, doesn&amp;rsquo;t have that parameter anymore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use Bing Desktop Wallpapers as background images in Teams calls</title>
      <link>https://www.007ffflearning.com/post/use-bing-wallpaper-as-background-in-teams/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.007ffflearning.com/post/use-bing-wallpaper-as-background-in-teams/</guid>
      <description>A few days ago, I blogged about Bing Desktop Wallpapers, a nice little tool you can install on your Windows Machine to enjoy some of the amazing views of the world.
Knowing these got stored on your local machine as JPEGs (C:\Users&amp;lt;user&amp;gt;\AppData\Local\Microsoft\BingWallpaperApp\WPImages), got me the idea to reuse these as &amp;ldquo;Teams Backgrounds&amp;rdquo; during video calls.
As the Bing Wallpaper gets updated every day, it would be nice to have a different image in Teams&amp;hellip; every day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Collecting Hugo static site statistics using Azure Application Insights</title>
      <link>https://www.007ffflearning.com/post/hugo_site_statistics_app_insights/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.007ffflearning.com/post/hugo_site_statistics_app_insights/</guid>
      <description>Welcome back!
About a month ago, I decided to move my former 007FFFLearning website from Wix.com to something &amp;ldquo;easier&amp;rdquo; to use for blog writing. While Wix is an excellent platform, offering an easy way to build a graphical website, besides a ton of plug-ins, it also comes with a cost. And since I didn&amp;rsquo;t have a need for a lot of the built-in features I was using out of my own business before I joined Microsoft, I wanted to try something new.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Running an Azure Storage Static Site, protected by Azure Front Door</title>
      <link>https://www.007ffflearning.com/post/static_site_frontdoor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.007ffflearning.com/post/static_site_frontdoor/</guid>
      <description>Earlier this week, I had the honor to present a session for the Belgian MC2MC Microsoft community, as part of a broader online event week with other Belgian community User Groups (https://www.mc2mc.be/events/be-community-week-mc2mc-evening).
My session topic was based on a little real-life project I worked on myself only a few weeks ago, deploying a “Hugo” based static website on Azure Storage Account Static Site (Yes, this site you are reading right now&amp;hellip;).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bing Desktop Wallpapers take you on a trip around the world</title>
      <link>https://www.007ffflearning.com/post/bing-wallpaper/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.007ffflearning.com/post/bing-wallpaper/</guid>
      <description>Due to COVID19, my traveling rhythm went down from an avg 90% the last six years, to 0%. I have never been that much at home without travel than in these last 5 weeks (and a few more to come).
While the primary reason for my travel is business related, every now and then, I have the opportunity to enjoy the area, if even only for a short moment, or in-between delivering sessions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My 1st 6 months as an Azure Technical Trainer at Microsoft</title>
      <link>https://www.007ffflearning.com/post/my-first-6-months-as-att/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.007ffflearning.com/post/my-first-6-months-as-att/</guid>
      <description>Hey,
It has been quiet for several weeks on the blog front, but that doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean nothing happened! The core subject of this post is sharing my happiness around being in the Azure Technical Trainer role for more than 6 months now. (Last time I was at Microsoft in 2016, this was about the time where I figured out I needed to move out of the team, exploring other opportunities&amp;hellip;) but not so this time!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New book published: Azure Strategy and Implementation Guide, 3rd edition</title>
      <link>https://www.007ffflearning.com/post/new-book-published/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.007ffflearning.com/post/new-book-published/</guid>
      <description>You might get amazed, finding out I managed to publish yet another book, where the previous one Efficiently Migrating your workloads to Azure only got published around Christmas.
However, this new one was a &amp;ldquo;longer work in progress&amp;rdquo;, and not something I could spew out in just a few weeks.
Several months ago, I got approached by Packt Publishing, asking me to &amp;ldquo;write a quick note on how I look at Azure strategic implementation and migration&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Updated Azure Exams Announced</title>
      <link>https://www.007ffflearning.com/post/updated-azure-exams/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.007ffflearning.com/post/updated-azure-exams/</guid>
      <description>Things are going fast in the Azure world, and apparently exams are more and more following that pace. Before you start screaming and worrying, as you might be preparing for a current exam, let me share a bit about several steps happening before an exam becomes available.
Exam Objectives (OD) For a long time, Microsoft Learning has based exams on &amp;ldquo;exam objectives&amp;rdquo;, which is typically a list of &amp;ldquo;services, features, activities&amp;rdquo; anyone taking the exam, should master.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy to announce my newest Azure book got (self) published</title>
      <link>https://www.007ffflearning.com/post/new-azure-book-selfpublish/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.007ffflearning.com/post/new-azure-book-selfpublish/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m excited about this next project that finally got live, thanks to a bit of quiet time during the Holidays. While it is not up to the full 100% of what I had in mind, I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to hold back the content any longer, since Azure is moving already that fast&amp;hellip;
The original idea of this material was based on a workshop I created for Microsoft Internal (Azure Developer Series) in Sept 2018 as a contractor, which was a combination of slides, videos and lab guides.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Azure Mystery Mansion</title>
      <link>https://www.007ffflearning.com/post/azure-mystery-mansion/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.007ffflearning.com/post/azure-mystery-mansion/</guid>
      <description>Earlier this week, I discovered &amp;quot;[Azure Mystery Mansion]https://www.microsoft.com/mysterymansion&amp;rdquo;, published by the Microsoft Azure marketing team. As an Azure enthusiast, I wanted to find out about this mystery ;), actually being really excited about it, as it is primarily focused around giving you an easy, fun, yet interesting learning experience.
What is it? It heavily reminded me of several PC games I played as a teenager (yes, early &amp;rsquo;90s), where you could move around a game, and even deciding on the flow and ending, by clicking keywords.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Azure Learning Resources</title>
      <link>https://www.007ffflearning.com/post/azure-learning-resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.007ffflearning.com/post/azure-learning-resources/</guid>
      <description>As I got asked so many times what Azure learning resources are available, I thought this could make up an excellent blog post :) - This is actually based on a summary slide I have added to my in-person and online Azure training workshops closing deck, but updated where needed. Below order is a random listing of resources, not forcing any priority or preference:
  Microsoft Learn
  Microsoft Hands-on Labs</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My 1st quarter as an Azure Technical Trainer at Microsoft</title>
      <link>https://www.007ffflearning.com/post/1st-quarter-as-att/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.007ffflearning.com/post/1st-quarter-as-att/</guid>
      <description>Hey,
As most of you probably know in meantime, I joined Microsoft as a full-time employee mid September this year, in the prestigious Azure Technical Trainer team - EMEA. This team is part of the WorldWide Learning (WWL) organization, and working on the Enterprise Skills Initiative (ESI) program.
As the name says, as Azure Technical Trainer, my role is to provide training to larger Microsoft Partners and customers in EMEA, helping them in being successful in using Azure, and mainly focusing on skilling up the IT teams (sysadmins, developers, solution architects).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Azure Hands On Labs</title>
      <link>https://www.007ffflearning.com/azurehol/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.007ffflearning.com/azurehol/</guid>
      <description>Azure Hands On Labs Registration form Please use this link to register for our Azure Hands On Labs. (Note: Only register when you signed up for a training session.
You can reach me by email peter at pdtit dot be or on Twitter @pdtit or @007FFFLearning if you have any questions or want to get access.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to 007FFFLearning.com</title>
      <link>https://www.007ffflearning.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.007ffflearning.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi, my name is Peter De Tender. I am an Azure Technical Trainer (ATT) at Microsoft. Out of this role, I provide Azure readiness workshops to larger Microsoft customers and partners in EMEA, skilling up their Azure knowledge, and preparing them for Azure certification. Before taking on this position, I was already an Azure trainer and Azure Solution Architect out of my own business, with a background in Microsoft datacenter consulting (Exchange, Forefront, System Center and Active Directory security as prime technologies, besides HP Servers and NetApp Storage :).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>